<jobs>
  <job>
    <title>
      Teller
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=101&amp;ao=63585&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1aef453e99f6d00c0&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109758&amp;jobListingId=1396977990
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Citizens Bank
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sr. VP, Marketing
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=101&amp;ao=65877&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109762&amp;jobListingId=1405956756
    </website>
    <location>
      King of Prussia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      ReminderMedia
    </cName>
    <description>
      Sr. VP, MarketingReminderMedia, publishers of American Lifestyle magazine, a growing King of Prussia based company is currently hiring. We help businesses solidify the key relationships that are driving their business. Due to growth, we have a unique opportunity for a Sr. VP, Marketing. The Sr. VP, Marketing is responsible for developing and executing strategies that measurably drive growth, improve customer retention, increase revenue, improve brand awareness and advance brand image. The Sr. VP, Marketing provides executive leadership and delivers integrated marketing and advertising strategies that achieve business results.Duties and responsibilities include but are not limited to the following:• Work with the CEO, Sales Manager and executive leadership team to address the most urgent resource optimization issues including product transformation, organizational change, and core competency needs.• Identify, articulate, and address strategic issues that affect company growth and sustainability, including company mission and vision; adoption of a market- and mission-driven philosophy; products, pricing, distribution and related topics.• Serve in a leadership role with bottom-line accountability for product management, marketing, and sales/business development functions. Will also maintain leadership role in resource optimization initiative, setting objectives, directing activities, and ensuring successful outcomes.• Regularly perform market penetration and competitive analysis by customer channel and recommend strategies to improve market position, improve quality, and reduce costs.• Develop an annual marketing plan in support of organizational strategy objectives. Establish and implement short and long-term goals, objectives, policies and operating procedures.• Oversee marketing communications including branding, public relations, advertising, white papers, trade shows, seminars and events collateral materials, analysis and market research management, website design and content, webinar development, and social media programs.• Partner with the management team to ensure the best possible service and effective communications with customers.• Provide input and support to company leadership in the development of joint ventures, affiliations, and partnership arrangements.• Create a company-wide marketing reporting function that can track, measure, and analyze performance.• Promote positive relations with partners, vendors, and distributors.• Other related duties as may be assigned by the CEO or COO.Qualifications:• Bachelor’s Degree in related discipline with specialized leadership training and/or demonstrated capability to perform job responsibilities through previous experience and education. Graduate degree preferred. • A minimum of ten (10) years of senior leadership experience in marketing and sales management, specifically in business to business marketing. • Deep experience in the areas of information-driven marketing to include CRM, sales leads management, implementation of social media lead generation programs etc. Working knowledge of advance analytical modeling.• A proven track record of success developing marketing and advertising strategies that drive traffic, increase customer retention, increase revenues, improve brand awareness and advance brand image.• Experience directing and using marketing research in program development and evaluation.• Previous experience in Real-estate and/or Finance a plus. • Some travel may be required.• Strong understanding of the digital/interactive marketing space.We help business professionals connect with their core clients, on a consistent basis, in order to help them generate repeat and referral business. If you’d like to learn more about ReminderMedia, we encourage you to check us out online at www.remindermedia.com. See what we do, how we do it, and why it works!Please apply through our website or via the link below:http://chc.tbe.taleo.net/chc05/ats/careers/requisition.jsp?org=REMIMEDI&amp;cws=1&amp;rid=344
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      iOS Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=102&amp;ao=65788&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109767&amp;jobListingId=1404794200
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Yinzcam
    </cName>
    <description>
      Who are we, and what are we looking for?
      YinzCam is the industry-leading mobile developer for sports-team apps in the United States, with clients in most major professional sports leagues such as the NFL, NBA, NHL, MLS, and even international clients such as the Australian National Rugby League. We are experiencing a period of significant growth in our business, and are looking to add more full-time Android developers.
      You will have the opportunity to work in a team of highly-skilled and experienced mobile developers to build and launch mobile apps that will be promoted by sports teams/stadiums as their official mobile app, and that will, therefore, be in the hands of millions of fans around the world. You will work closely with designers and back-end developers in a collaborative environment to develop compelling applications that provide real-time statistics and media content from official league and team source data feeds, while continuing to evolve and enhance application interfaces and improve user experience. You will also have the opportunity to innovate and explore new features such as gaming, augmented reality, etc.
      
      Perks
      You will have the opportunity to travel to stadiums/arenas around the country (and potentially overseas) to see how sports technology works behind the scenes. You will be exposed to the sports industry and all aspects of the company's business, including licensing, sales, advertising, revenue generation, etc. You will work in a company that invests significantly in the training of its personnel, with staff being routinely encouraged to attend professional-development and training conferences to hone and extend their skills. Benefits include competitive salaries and medical+dental insurance.
      
      Why are we hiring?
      
      We are currently expanding rapidly to take on even more clients, more teams/stadiums and more sports, including overseas, and we are looking to grow our mobile team by adding full-time iOS developers to meet the demand for our products, and to bring even more innovations and features to our existing mobile offerings. Our company affords a close-knit entrepreneurial environment with every individual being exposed to, and having a tangible impact on, the company's business.
      Come join us, and you will be a part of developing the ultimate mobile experience for sports fans everywhere!
      
      Desired Skills and Experience Required:
      At least 2 years' experience programming with iOS (iOS SDK, Objective C)
      Experience with advanced UI implementation
      API experience with client-server programming and multimedia playback
      Proficiency with XCode
      Experience with SVN and Git
      Experience with XML and JSON
      Highly desirable:
      SQLite API experience a plus
      Experience with one or more scripting languages
      Experience with interfacing with designers and content/feed administrators
      Have at least one app that you developed (or contributed substantially to) and released in the Apple App Store.
      Please send your resume to jobs@yinzcam.com and highlight
      Your overall technical skills and background
      Your relevant professional and academic experience
      Your mobile-app development skills (mention example projects, number of months of experience)
      Your mobile-web development skills (mention example projects, number of months of experience)
      Your system-integration skills, e.g., working with SDKs, APIs
      Your software-engineering skills, e.g., version control, testing
      Links to mobile apps that you have helped to create in the Apple App Store (mention how many others on the team, and what your role was in creating the app)
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      UberX Driver Partner (Full Time Independent Contractor)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=103&amp;ao=65247&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109770&amp;jobListingId=1407693408
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Uber
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sort Observation for Package Handler Positions
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=104&amp;ao=63871&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109774&amp;jobListingId=1407302445
    </website>
    <location>
      Lewisberry, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      FedEx Ground
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Site Reliability Engineer / Linux
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=105&amp;ao=57516&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109779&amp;jobListingId=1406439746
    </website>
    <location>
      Bethlehem, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Synchronoss
    </cName>
    <description>
      Overview Site Reliability Engineer (SREs) is integrated within the infrastructure team, and were looking for engineers who want to be a part of developing infrastructure, maintaining it, and scaling it. As a Site Reliability Engineer (SRE) you will have proven experience in supporting mission-critical 24/7/365 IT cloud-based and virtual computing infrastructures, and internal/external end-users. Requirements: At least 4 years of Linux system administration and support experience in an enterprise IT environment. Hands on experience including, but not limited to: Strong AWS experience across the full breadth of AWS technologies. Linux OS Administration, preferably RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL 5 and 6). Ability to troubleshoot java server applications (Tomcat) and APIs in distributed environments. Apache deployment, tuning, and support. Experience with Zabbix or Nagios or similar monitoring solutions. Ability to script in at least one of the following: Shell, Perl, or Python. Oracle and MySQL Database administration from an operations standpoint. Working with storage solutions (Netapp, Isilon, EMC) using iSCSI and NFS.
      Responsibilities: Monitor site reliability and performance while improving the quality of our infrastructure Work with ticketing systems &amp; troubleshoot site down issues Create and maintain technical documentation Scale infrastructure to meet demand Document system design Communicate effectively with other engineers, teams, and business partners Participate in on-call rotation
      Education or Equivalent Experience:
      o Bachelors degree or equivalent experience
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Teller
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=106&amp;ao=63585&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109785&amp;jobListingId=1407474322
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Citizens Bank
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Pharmacy Technician - Specialty Pharmacy
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=107&amp;ao=47682&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109791&amp;jobListingId=1405923130
    </website>
    <location>
      Monroeville, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      CVS Health
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      RN Imaging
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=108&amp;ao=65658&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109796&amp;jobListingId=1406254081
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Cancer Treatment Centers of America
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Roll Off Driver Class B CDL
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=109&amp;ao=65311&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109801&amp;jobListingId=1406096262
    </website>
    <location>
      West Grove, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Republic Services
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Applications Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=110&amp;ao=65822&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1b2673b60989a548c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109805&amp;jobListingId=1407269109
    </website>
    <location>
      Scranton, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      UPS
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Route Sales Management/Distributor, Full Training
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=101&amp;ao=57756&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1939605e16794bb20&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109810&amp;jobListingId=1365460133
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Mac Tools
    </cName>
    <description>
      Start building your career and future now!Mac Tools was founded in 1938 in Sabina, OH. Today, Mac Tools is an international business with Distributors and Franchisees in the United States, Canada, Europe and Japan and is part of Stanley Black &amp; Decker, Inc., a brand synonymous with quality and impeccable customer service.Today, Mac Tools has a product line in excess of 42,000 items, and still uses the direct sales approach with a mobile sales force of distributors. The Mac Tools philosophy of excellent quality, price and service remains unchanged over the years, and the company spirit that made them successful in 1938, is the same spirit that makes them a leader in the automotive tool and equipment business todayWE CURRENTLY HAVE A LOCAL ROUTE AVAILABLE.________________________________________EVERYTHING YOU NEED TO BUILD A SUCCESSFUL BUSINESS IS HERE:No cold calls.No Experience necessary, we will train youUnique Route &amp; Territory (Approx 325 customers)Your Mac Tools truck, which will become your own personal mobile tool storeInitial Inventory of top-selling, high-transaction toolsMobile Business Software to manage your businessFinancing for Qualified CandidatesWorking capital to help your business growNational marketing support________________________________________NO EXPERIENCE NECESSARYYou don't need an automotive tools background to be a high-performing franchisee. People from all walks-of-life have found success with the Mac Tools brand!UNPARALLELED TRAININGIt all begins with Tool School at our headquarters in Ohio. Here, Mac Tools professionals apply over 75 years of experience in the mobile tool industry to provide you with the training you need to get started.After Tool School, your District Manager will ride with you on your route for ten days offering sales and business training. They will assist in merchandising your truck and help to implement the promotional techniques that can increase sales at every stop.LOW START UP COSTWe understand that starting your own business can be financially trying. With our low start-up costs, for qualified individuals, we offer a variety of options to fit your unique financial needs.AWARD WINNING#1 New Franchise 2014 Entrepreneur.com#3 Fastest Growing Franchise 2014 Entrepreneur.comTop 100 Franchise 2014 Entrepreneur.comOVER 75 YEARS OF KNOWLEDGEMac Tools® has been operating in mobile tool distribution for over 75 years, creating a well-established brand with a long history and heritage. In this time, we have refined the model to help you be successful as a franchisee.Additionally, Mac Tools® has the power of Stanley Black &amp; Decker Inc. behind us, allowing us to be stronger than ever.ON YOUR OWN, BUT NOT ALONEAs a Mac Tools Franchisee, you'll discover that, although you operate an independent business, you're far from being alone. You'll have one of the most extensive support systems in the industry right at your fingertips.Customer serviceTechnical serviceOngoing Field Excellence Meetings every eight weeksCustomer Credit ProgramDISCOVER MAC TOOLS!Once your application is approved, we will send you on a Discovery Day with an already successful Mac Tools franchise owner so that you can learn more about the mobile tool business. These events will help you to experience the business and learn about the full potential of the opportunity. There is no cost or obligation to participate in a Discovery Day.So what are you waiting for? If you've always aspired to run your own business and be a part of one of the leading mobile tool companies in the industry, then you owe it to yourself to learn more today!________________________________________IMPORTANT NOTE: We have limited routes available in some areas. So don't delay, send your resume today before the open route in your area has been filled.ASK US ABOUT OUR SPECIAL INCENTIVES AVAILABLE FOR VETSMac Tools®, a division of Stanley Black &amp; Decker Inc.505 N Cleveland Ave.Westerville, Ohio 43082The offer of a franchise can only be made through the delivery of a Franchise Disclosure Document. Certain jurisdictions require registration prior to the offer or sale of a franchise. We do not offer franchises in jurisdictions where we are not registered (or exempt from registration)  Apply on Career Site
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Pharmacy Technician - Specialty Pharmacy
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=102&amp;ao=47682&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbd1b1939605e16794bb20&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697109814&amp;jobListingId=1357679585
    </website>
    <location>
      Monroeville, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      CVS Health
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Machine Learning Engineer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=201&amp;ao=38150&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae82476083e5763e8b&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119443&amp;jobListingId=1342794118
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Turnitin.com
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Regional Planning Consultant
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=202&amp;ao=65671&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae82476083e5763e8b&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119448&amp;jobListingId=1387149531
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Fidelity Investments
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Territory Sales Manager, SUSE, Pennsylvania &amp; New Jersey
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=201&amp;ao=40001&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119452&amp;jobListingId=1407560401
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      SUSE
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      National Account Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=202&amp;ao=55296&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119456&amp;jobListingId=1405721346
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      American Textile
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      RN - Canonsburg, PA
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=203&amp;ao=56889&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119461&amp;jobListingId=1407165121
    </website>
    <location>
      Canonsburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Fresenius Medical Care - North America
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Director of Admissions - Multi Facility
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=204&amp;ao=47072&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119466&amp;jobListingId=1407132804
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Consulate Health Care
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Staff Accountant
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=205&amp;ao=60961&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119470&amp;jobListingId=1406822841
    </website>
    <location>
      Malvern, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Frontline Technologies
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sr Account Executive
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=206&amp;ao=59676&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119477&amp;jobListingId=1404867479
    </website>
    <location>
      Pennsylvania
    </location>
    <cName>
      Gartner
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      IT Project Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=207&amp;ao=45587&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119480&amp;jobListingId=1406234754
    </website>
    <location>
      Breinigsville, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Buckeye Partners
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Registered Nurse (RN) Pediatric Paoli
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=208&amp;ao=62246&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119485&amp;jobListingId=1407273134
    </website>
    <location>
      Havertown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      BAYADA Home Health Care
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Service Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=209&amp;ao=60961&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119489&amp;jobListingId=1405611472
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Springboard Media
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Geospatial Intern Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=210&amp;ao=48269&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7ae989237e2a8675905&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119491&amp;jobListingId=1407262214
    </website>
    <location>
      Camp Hill, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Gannett Fleming
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Highway Project Engineer/Asst. Project Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=201&amp;ao=63199&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7aea91127c89ba64593&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119496&amp;jobListingId=1394316288
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      TranSystems
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Account Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=202&amp;ao=44581&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fbf7aea91127c89ba64593&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697119500&amp;jobListingId=1356569860
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Branding Brand
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sales Engineer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=301&amp;ao=48042&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8cbe916bfe2742d3&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127627&amp;jobListingId=1217706210
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Bit9 + Carbon Black
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Compliance Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=302&amp;ao=55296&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8cbe916bfe2742d3&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127630&amp;jobListingId=1388484591
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      American Textile
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Designated Support Engineer (DSE)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=301&amp;ao=56389&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127633&amp;jobListingId=1407758588
    </website>
    <location>
      Reading, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      FireEye
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Area Service Technician
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=302&amp;ao=50785&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127637&amp;jobListingId=1405198654
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Electric Guard Dog
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sales Account Manager- Southeastern
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=303&amp;ao=54332&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127641&amp;jobListingId=1406049063
    </website>
    <location>
      Gilbertsville, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Waste Management
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Operations Finance Analyst
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=304&amp;ao=62771&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127644&amp;jobListingId=1406947146
    </website>
    <location>
      Harrisburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Cameron Craig Group
    </cName>
    <description>
      Providing financial performance reporting and analysis support for manufacturing sites;
      Business forecasting – weekly and monthly financial statement outlooks;
      Assisting in the preparation of short-term and long-term operating plans;
      Examining business model and cost structure to identify areas for opportunity and business improvement;
      Make vs. buy analysis for Supply Chain Optimization;
      Standardizing metrics and financial system setup - Systems Development and Maintenance;
      Continuous Improvement of financial processes and reporting.
      Education: 4-year degree required; Accounting, Finance, Business Management or related disciplines preferred. Required Skills:      3+ years of experience in financial analysis;
      Experience in a manufacturing or supply chain environment;
      Must have experience in operational accounting and ability to meet operational metrics;
      Strong analytical skills, desire to probe facts, identify and question assumptions, and analyze issues from different perspectives;
      Working knowledge of general accounting, income statement, balance sheet, standard cost accounting, and cost systems.
      Apply on Partner Site
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Information Specialist
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=305&amp;ao=56854&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127648&amp;jobListingId=1405570213
    </website>
    <location>
      Malvern, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      FM Global
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Call Coordinator
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=306&amp;ao=64336&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127656&amp;jobListingId=1406822536
    </website>
    <location>
      Pennsylvania
    </location>
    <cName>
      CompuCom
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Transporter - Centran - Full-Time - 3pm-11:30pm
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=307&amp;ao=61172&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127660&amp;jobListingId=1406809735
    </website>
    <location>
      West Reading, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Reading Health System
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Copywriter hot
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=308&amp;ao=64836&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127665&amp;jobListingId=1408001208
    </website>
    <location>
      Newtown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      EPAM
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Senior Apparel Designer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=309&amp;ao=40339&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127670&amp;jobListingId=1405322798
    </website>
    <location>
      Warren, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Blair Corporation
    </cName>
    <description>
      Company Description It all started with a simple black raincoat.
      The year was 1910. Young John Blair, a law student at the University of Pennsylvania, was approached by a fellow student who had recently inherited a raincoat factory. Would he be interested in being a sales manager? Easter vacation and a train ride home to Warren was all the time John needed to make his decision.
      With a suitcase of black raincoats in hand, he approached clothing store owners along his way. In one nearby town, he sold a lone coat to a customer an undertaker. But the shop owner was reluctant to carry any more raincoats for just a few local undertakers.
      John Blair was not about to give up. He decided the best way to reach the new market he had just created in his own mind the market of undertakers who would certainly wear black raincoats was by mail. So with just $500 borrowed capital, he printed and mailed flyers across the country. And he sold 1200 raincoats in no time! Thus, the New Process Company was created.
      Over 100 years later, we've grown to offer exceptional clothing for women and men, plus quality items for your home. We've changed our name to simply, Blair. But we still proudly serve customers across the country. And we still maintain the high standards that John Blair built the company on so many years ago.
      Our company headquarters is still located in the small town of Warren, Pennsylvania. We're proud of our heritage, our employees and our hometown!
      For more information on Blair and our parent company, Orchard Brands, please visit http://orchardbrands.com/ or www.blair.com
      Job Description Description:
      An exciting opportunity for a seasoned Senior Apparel Design Professional with experience in the design of seasonal collections of Ready to Wear in all classifications of fabrications.
      Working with the merchandising team in clarifying the brands identity for multiple labels of business.
      Developing custom palettes, prints and motifs that express each specific labels Brand Identity.
      Duties:
      • Responsible for managing the design process from conception through to final styling for assigned product category.
      • Responsible for product design process to include market research, conceptual presentations, design and guidance through fabric, print, spec and fit processes.
      • Responsible for researching markets in order to identify new trends, fabrics, techniques, etc.
      • Actively participates in the conceptual development of product lines (i.e., sells ideas/concepts and convinces others to adopt a course of action).
      • Works with technical designer and pre-production partner to ensure design packages are complete and accurate.
      • Resolves developmental issues to ensure the workflow meets corporate time and action calendar requirements and monitors critical dates to ensure seasonal product is on schedule.
      • Seasonal travel for research and/or product development is required.
      Qualifications Qualifications:
      • Bachelors degree in Fashion Design or in a related field, preferably with a concentration in the field of both artistic and technical design.
      • Thorough knowledge of silhouettes, fabrication, color use, sewing techniques, graphics and trim
      • Strong design and conceptual skills
      • 4-6 years design experience
      • Ability to hand sketch
      Key Technical Experience:
      • Strong computer knowledge including Adobe Illustrator and Microsoft Excel.
      • Ability to hand sketch
      • Artistic skills are a must
      Additional Information
      Physical Requirements:
      While performing the duties of this job, the employee is regularly required to sit and talk and hear. The employee frequently is required to use hands to operate a computer keyboard. The employee must occasionally lift and/or move up to 25 pounds. Specific vision abilities required by this job include close vision, distance vision, and color vision.
      Blair offers a competitive salary commensurate with experience and an excellent benefits package including Health/Dental insurance, Life, Long Term and Short Term Disability Insurance, Flexible Spending Accounts, 401K Match, EAP, and Employee Discount. For consideration, please submit your resume, along with a cover letter and salary requirements.
      Blair is an equal opportunity employer.
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Primary Cell Operator (6)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=310&amp;ao=38682&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8eb2cd51d65529f8&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127675&amp;jobListingId=1407754548
    </website>
    <location>
      Concordville, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Southco
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Trainer, Retail Sales
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=301&amp;ao=57980&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8e0e572e77e5cc56&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127680&amp;jobListingId=1382240935
    </website>
    <location>
      West Mifflin, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Mosaic Sales Solutions
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Operations Admin I - III (Senior)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=302&amp;ao=56665&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc177a8e0e572e77e5cc56&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697127684&amp;jobListingId=1407397388
    </website>
    <location>
      Leetsdale, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      FedEx Ground
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      CDL DRIVER
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=401&amp;ao=61675&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde95ab6a28c6072c71&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138035&amp;jobListingId=1387229003
    </website>
    <location>
      Freedom, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      PoolCorp
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Inside Sales
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=402&amp;ao=61920&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde95ab6a28c6072c71&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138039&amp;jobListingId=1395507509
    </website>
    <location>
      Washington, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Insperity
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Nurse Manager - RN
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=401&amp;ao=65525&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138043&amp;jobListingId=1406451919
    </website>
    <location>
      Williamsport, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      HCR ManorCare
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Personal Loan Specialist
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=402&amp;ao=65472&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138047&amp;jobListingId=1407565839
    </website>
    <location>
      Hatfield, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Springleaf Finance
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Factory Sales Rep
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=403&amp;ao=63456&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138051&amp;jobListingId=1407486249
    </website>
    <location>
      Kittanning, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Klingspor
    </cName>
    <description>
      KLINGSPOR Abrasives, Inc., a manufacturer of the highest quality industrial sanding and grinding products is searching for an enthusiastic and self-motivated Factory Sales Representative based in the Kittanning, PA area. This Entry-Level position requires excellent written and verbal communication skills. You must possess the ability to work independently in a fast paced sales environment. Experience in industrial sales is a plus, but not required. We will train the right candidate in both technical and selling skills to be successful.   Qualifications/Responsibilities:  - Team player with a positive attitude  - Develop prospective customers and maintain current customers  - Ability to work entire sales process from prospecting to close  - Candidate MUST live within 20 miles of the territory  - An insurable driving record is required  - Highly motivated and results driven  - Energy and enthusiasm  - Sound judgment and decision making  - A commitment to outstanding customer service  - Attention to detail  - Some college coursework or commensurate experience   Base salary is $28,500 per year + Commission Unlimited Earning potential! We offer a great opportunity with competitive benefits which includes, Medical, Dental, and Vision Insurance, Short and Long Term Disability, Health Flex Spending Account, Life Insurance, 401k, 9 Paid Holidays, Paid Time Off, Year-end bonus, KLINGSPOR Award Program (KAP). Company cell phone, company laptop, and company car which includes maintenance expenses, insurance, and gas card. If this career opportunity interests you, we require you to submit your resume, cover letter and salary requirements. Serious inquires only please.
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Job Fair - CDL Drivers &amp; Dock Workers
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=404&amp;ao=66012&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138056&amp;jobListingId=1406263236
    </website>
    <location>
      Dunmore, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      New Penn Motor Express
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Application Engineer I
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=405&amp;ao=34032&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138060&amp;jobListingId=1406081727
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Big Heart Pet Brands
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Project Manager (E03 or E04)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=406&amp;ao=53889&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138141&amp;jobListingId=1405574977
    </website>
    <location>
      Middletown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Exelon
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Field Account Manager - K12
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=407&amp;ao=56561&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138146&amp;jobListingId=1407745757
    </website>
    <location>
      Harrisburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      CDW
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Quality Assurance Manager Clinical Packaging
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=408&amp;ao=32097&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138150&amp;jobListingId=1405971727
    </website>
    <location>
      Allentown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Thermo Fisher Scientific
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Senior Sales Representative - Retirement Services
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=409&amp;ao=32973&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138155&amp;jobListingId=1407845460
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Paychex
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Customer Service Representative
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=410&amp;ao=56873&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fde93780900e42ab1e5&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138159&amp;jobListingId=1407641335
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      HomeSmart
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Account Executive
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=401&amp;ao=52563&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fdeb092909435ec17d1&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138164&amp;jobListingId=1378366371
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Rewards Network
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Regional Director of Human Resources
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=402&amp;ao=47072&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc3fdeb092909435ec17d1&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697138169&amp;jobListingId=1269635964
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Consulate Health Care
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Digital Marketing Analyst
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=501&amp;ao=57234&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a7b72f0e809cc6c0&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152223&amp;jobListingId=1401465599
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Merkle
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sr Project Manager - Energy Efficiency / Performance Contracting
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=502&amp;ao=53888&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a7b72f0e809cc6c0&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152225&amp;jobListingId=1392486798
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Exelon
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Account Coordinator - Part Time
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=501&amp;ao=36358&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152228&amp;jobListingId=1406621378
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      vRide
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Front of House-Restaurant Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=502&amp;ao=58744&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152231&amp;jobListingId=1405137041
    </website>
    <location>
      Downingtown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Buffalo Wild Wings
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Leasing Manager - Chestnut Hill Village
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=503&amp;ao=63504&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152234&amp;jobListingId=1404696153
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      AIMCO Properties
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Education Coordinator - Southeastern Virginia
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=504&amp;ao=48055&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152237&amp;jobListingId=1407308219
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      American Public University System
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Senior Sales Specialist - RA - Western, PA
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=505&amp;ao=55696&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152240&amp;jobListingId=1405208495
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      UCB
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sales Development Representative
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=506&amp;ao=46760&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152244&amp;jobListingId=1405738992
    </website>
    <location>
      Harrisburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Phoenix Contact USA
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Account Executive Business Sales
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=507&amp;ao=57619&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152247&amp;jobListingId=1406782935
    </website>
    <location>
      Allentown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Verizon Wireless
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Field Sales Manager- Scranton, PA
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=508&amp;ao=57035&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152251&amp;jobListingId=1407565603
    </website>
    <location>
      Pennsylvania
    </location>
    <cName>
      Samsung Electronics America
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Claims Adjuster - Liability Br
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=509&amp;ao=60229&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152254&amp;jobListingId=1404872005
    </website>
    <location>
      Mechanicsburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Arthur J. Gallagher &amp; Co.
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      ES&amp;H Specialist
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=510&amp;ao=59574&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a02178b92600de52&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152257&amp;jobListingId=1405277925
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      AECOM
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sales Rep-Commission - Trench Safety
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=501&amp;ao=60797&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a8cf3cee1bf27d59&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152259&amp;jobListingId=1355463167
    </website>
    <location>
      West Mifflin, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      United Rentals
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      RN - Canonsburg, PA
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=502&amp;ao=56889&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc7793a8cf3cee1bf27d59&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697152262&amp;jobListingId=1407165121
    </website>
    <location>
      Canonsburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Fresenius Medical Care - North America
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      UberX Driver Partner (Part Time Independent Contractor)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=601&amp;ao=65247&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d38b93d9a797aba178&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157100&amp;jobListingId=1407693449
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Uber
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Management Trainee (Sales &amp; Recruiting)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=602&amp;ao=64197&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d38b93d9a797aba178&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157103&amp;jobListingId=1383695450
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Peak Technical Staffing USA
    </cName>
    <description>
      Management Trainee Program
      (Recruiting &amp; Sales)
      
      
      Who are we?
      
      PEAK Technical Staffing continues to be the technical staffing firm of choice for the nation's largest companies. We are a nationally recognized provider of skilled technical professionals to corporations nationwide. At PEAK we provide the opportunity for you to grow and choose your career path. PEAK began in 1968 and has grown as a family-owned and operated business since 1968, with offices all over the country and plans to open new offices each year.
      
      Our ability to place the right people in the right place at the right time enables our customers to expand and reduce their staff with temporary contract professionals when the need arises. It also provides our customers with the advantage of using our recruiting expertise to provide direct hire candidates for proprietary positions while being able to offer our candidates the best jobs available in the technical marketplace.
      
      Why us?
      
      PEAK offers great opportunities for advancement, personal and professional growth, and unlimited earning potential. PEAK grew at a greater pace than the rest of the staffing industry in 2014 and we are poised for growth in the future. We are big enough to offer great opportunity and career path, and small enough that your hard work will be noticed and rewarded as you quickly advance through the ranks at PEAK.
      
      PEAK seeks professional individuals with competitive spirit, drive, team mentality, courage, and commitment, who have demonstrated perseverance and are looking to build a long term career in a sales driven environment. Benefits of joining our team include:
      Growth potential within the organization including a defined career path into recruiting and sales for college graduates
      Thorough training on recruiting and sales with a concentration on technical industry (no previous technical knowledge necessary)
      Opportunities for continued education and education assistance
      Dynamic and diverse culture with a team-oriented environment
      Unlimited earning potential, including a competitive base salary after paid training period and uncapped commission structure
      
      
      Job Duties Include:
      Develop recruiting strategies designed to identify qualified candidates through various recruiting tools.
      Evaluate candidates’ strengths compared with clients’ requirements by, for example, evaluating, screening, and interviewing the candidate.
      Negotiate wages, terms and conditions of employment with candidates, and gain commitment from candidates for current and future job requirements.
      Manage contract employees while on assignment. Assess and investigate contractor related problems, and administer performance counseling, coaching, and disciplinary measures when necessary.
      Work with Account Managers to identify top accounts, target skill sets, key market segments, and to assess clients’ staffing requirements.
      Communicate effectively with others in order to create a productive and diverse environment.
      Communicate with peers by sharing recruiting “best practices” and providing accurate, thorough documentation on contract employees in applicant tracking systems or other documentation tools.
      Maintain relationships with industry contacts to provide customer service, gain industry knowledge, and get referrals and sales leads.Requirements:
      
      Must have a desire to build a career in sales
      Bachelor’s degree required; Business Administration, Marketing, Management, Engineering, IT or related field preferred.
      Prior experience in service-oriented sales is preferred
      Excellent written and oral communication skills
      A sense of urgency, excellent presentation skills, and a high standard of professionalism and character
      A desire to learn, teach, and lead
      
      Comprehensive Benefits Package
      
      After training period is complete, employees receive a competitive base salary, commission, and a benefits package including a 401(k) retirement savings plan and vacation, personal, and holiday pay.
      Medical – Cigna Preferred Provider Organization (PPO) with a Health Savings Account (HSA)
      Dental – United Concordia Dental Plan
      Vision - Highmark
      Insurance – Life and Accidental Death &amp; Dismemberment (AD&amp;D)
      
      Additional Benefits Include:
      Short-term and long-term disability
      Dependent Care Flexible Spending Account
      Education Assistance
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Enterprise Account Executive - Service Provider
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=601&amp;ao=65258&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157105&amp;jobListingId=1405565263
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Apigee
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Senior Principal Software Ninja Dell SecureWorks
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=602&amp;ao=64059&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157108&amp;jobListingId=1407762443
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Dell
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Android Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=603&amp;ao=44583&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157111&amp;jobListingId=1405651255
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Branding Brand
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Retail Sales - At Home (Wit &amp; Wonder) - Ross Park
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=604&amp;ao=61313&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157115&amp;jobListingId=1406263818
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Nordstrom
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Detailer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=605&amp;ao=30654&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157118&amp;jobListingId=1405678539
    </website>
    <location>
      Cranberry Township, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      CarSense
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Critical Care Tech - Jefferson Hospital for Neuroscience - Neuro ICU
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=606&amp;ao=62741&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157123&amp;jobListingId=1406988841
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Thomas Jefferson University Hospital
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Load Puller Store Seasonal Employee
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=607&amp;ao=60428&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157126&amp;jobListingId=1406921409
    </website>
    <location>
      Lancaster, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Lowe's
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Franchise Sales Director, ERA Real Estate
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=608&amp;ao=54665&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157129&amp;jobListingId=1407848402
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Realogy
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Printing Channel Sales Manager-Mid Atlantic
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=609&amp;ao=35968&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157131&amp;jobListingId=1404961941
    </website>
    <location>
      Plymouth Meeting, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Zebra Technologies
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Agency Operator
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=610&amp;ao=56522&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3bca6a4a3131da2fe&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157134&amp;jobListingId=1406467479
    </website>
    <location>
      Center, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Avis Budget Group
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      iOS Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=601&amp;ao=65788&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3afd07e64d0d06abf&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157138&amp;jobListingId=1404794200
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Yinzcam
    </cName>
    <description>
      Who are we, and what are we looking for?
      YinzCam is the industry-leading mobile developer for sports-team apps in the United States, with clients in most major professional sports leagues such as the NFL, NBA, NHL, MLS, and even international clients such as the Australian National Rugby League. We are experiencing a period of significant growth in our business, and are looking to add more full-time Android developers.
      You will have the opportunity to work in a team of highly-skilled and experienced mobile developers to build and launch mobile apps that will be promoted by sports teams/stadiums as their official mobile app, and that will, therefore, be in the hands of millions of fans around the world. You will work closely with designers and back-end developers in a collaborative environment to develop compelling applications that provide real-time statistics and media content from official league and team source data feeds, while continuing to evolve and enhance application interfaces and improve user experience. You will also have the opportunity to innovate and explore new features such as gaming, augmented reality, etc.
      
      Perks
      You will have the opportunity to travel to stadiums/arenas around the country (and potentially overseas) to see how sports technology works behind the scenes. You will be exposed to the sports industry and all aspects of the company's business, including licensing, sales, advertising, revenue generation, etc. You will work in a company that invests significantly in the training of its personnel, with staff being routinely encouraged to attend professional-development and training conferences to hone and extend their skills. Benefits include competitive salaries and medical+dental insurance.
      
      Why are we hiring?
      
      We are currently expanding rapidly to take on even more clients, more teams/stadiums and more sports, including overseas, and we are looking to grow our mobile team by adding full-time iOS developers to meet the demand for our products, and to bring even more innovations and features to our existing mobile offerings. Our company affords a close-knit entrepreneurial environment with every individual being exposed to, and having a tangible impact on, the company's business.
      Come join us, and you will be a part of developing the ultimate mobile experience for sports fans everywhere!
      
      Desired Skills and Experience Required:
      At least 2 years' experience programming with iOS (iOS SDK, Objective C)
      Experience with advanced UI implementation
      API experience with client-server programming and multimedia playback
      Proficiency with XCode
      Experience with SVN and Git
      Experience with XML and JSON
      Highly desirable:
      SQLite API experience a plus
      Experience with one or more scripting languages
      Experience with interfacing with designers and content/feed administrators
      Have at least one app that you developed (or contributed substantially to) and released in the Apple App Store.
      Please send your resume to jobs@yinzcam.com and highlight
      Your overall technical skills and background
      Your relevant professional and academic experience
      Your mobile-app development skills (mention example projects, number of months of experience)
      Your mobile-web development skills (mention example projects, number of months of experience)
      Your system-integration skills, e.g., working with SDKs, APIs
      Your software-engineering skills, e.g., version control, testing
      Links to mobile apps that you have helped to create in the Apple App Store (mention how many others on the team, and what your role was in creating the app)
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Full Stack Javascript Web Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=602&amp;ao=63878&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fc89d3afd07e64d0d06abf&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697157139&amp;jobListingId=1379874376
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Wahila Creative
    </cName>
    <description>
      About UsWe focus on web applications for desktop and mobile, but in reality we take on all sizes and shapes of projects...
      Our services include everything from visual to interaction design, from schema design to platform specifications, and from development to long-term support (well, sometimes).
      We recently launched the Green Light Foods app with Phipps Conservatory and Botinical Gardens; a stock market visualization tool for Equivane; and a real-time status display used to track robotic forklifts (sorry, can't share that one).
      When we’re not building web apps, we’re building complex WordPress-driven sites for air curtain manufacturers (huh?) or maybe just bird watching (bald eagles, to be precise).
      In short, we tackle a wide range of projects, with a small team, and have fun while doing it.
      About YouJavascript on the client? check. Javascript on the server? check. We love it, and you do too.
      This position requires someone with a solid background in web development, but who isn't afraid to venture out of their comfort zone and learn something new. We love great design, creative solutions, and reusable code. We also like to laugh — mostly at ourselves.
      Typical responsibilities include server-side development using node, express.js, and mongodb; building, and deploying code to, hosted instances; creating killer WordPress solutions that involve a technical as well as an aesthetic sensitivity; and generally solving problems with code.
      Required Skills/Experience:
      Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science, or 2+ years proven development experience.
      ESL (English as a Second Language) — since Javascript is clearly your first
      Demonstrable prowess with WordPress, Drupal, and/or other similar CMS.
      Ability to build a responsive site (desktop, tablet, phone).
      Prior Experience with any of the following is preferred — visual or interaction (UI/UX) experience; MEAN stacks; mobile application development (Cordova, Objective C, HTML5); MVC frameworks for web applications (such as Express or Code Igniter); test driven development; experience working with Object Oriented Design techniques; and command line interfaces (cli). The terminal is your friend.
      About the JobOur benefits include medical, dental, and vision insurance plans; and pre-tax commuter deductions. We offer a flexible work schedule and a casual dress work environment. We are a small (in number, not in height), collaborative, social, creative, and tech-savvy company.
      In short — Great people. Awesome projects. Flexible schedule. Coffee, Tea, Muffins, and more. Free corny jokes.
      Apply on Career Site
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      HVAC Service Technician
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=701&amp;ao=63617&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55f964400ae4b1fa7af&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167733&amp;jobListingId=1375124775
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      South Hills Electric Heating and Cooling
    </cName>
    <description>
      HVAC Service Technician (Pittsburgh) Call-412-251-4785 to discuss a position Well established heating cooling and electrical company in need of an experienced HVAC technician. TOP PAY, SIGN ON BONUS UP TO 2K, efficiency bonuses and YEAR ROUND WORK for QUALIFIED individuals. Start making what you're worth.........not what the industry standards offer!! Up to 100K yearly documented for top earners REQUIREMENTS: (as listed but not limited to)* Minimum 4 years’ experience with forced air furnaces and air conditioners/heat pumps* Basic electrical knowledge 110/220v circuitry* Boiler experience a plu$* Clean driving record a must* Clean appearance a must* Basic tin work experience a plu$* Ability to lead/teach graduates* Maintain a clean and organized work space/vehicle* Maintain inventory on truck to ensure install efficiency* Maintain professional attitude* Positive attitude and motivated outlook a MUST!!* Ability to communicate well with customers and co-workers Compensation package:*Top pay per hour plus sales commission (unlimited earning potential)*Clean work environment *Company vehicle*Medical/ Dental and eye *Holiday and vacation pay*Paid training opportunities *Company supplied I phones
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Building Maintenance Technician
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=702&amp;ao=64624&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55f964400ae4b1fa7af&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167735&amp;jobListingId=1389910857
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Walnut Capital Management
    </cName>
    <description>
      Walnut Capital is looking for a Full-time Building Maintenance Technician for our Luxury Apartments throughout Pittsburgh. Walnut Capital offers a great opportunity for anyone interested in property management and customer service with one of Pittsburgh’s fastest growing real estate development companies.  Competitive wages plus Benefits: Health, Dental, Life, PTO Program, Holidays and 401k
      This position will perform a variety of skilled and semi-skilled maintenance duties for luxury multi-family housing facilities.
      Requirements:
      Basic plumbing, carpentry, electrical, HVAC, painting, grounds keeping, snow removal,
      Troubleshooting skills
      Competent use of hand and power tools
      Repair/maintenance of a variety of types of equipment
      3-5 years’ experience in a multi-family maintenance position
      Strong oral and written communication skills are a must
      Ability to provide excellent customer service
      Perform routine preventive maintenance
      Must have a valid driver’s license, proof of insurance and a good driving record.
      Ideal candidate will be hands on and technically knowledgeable in all aspects of multi-family maintenance including a comfort level with computers (MS Office) and smart phones.
      Candidates will work rotating On-Call duty, must be able to meet a 30 minute response time for On Call and/or emergencies. This position is located in the east end of Pittsburgh.
      Preference given to candidates with specialized skills in the following areas:
      HVAC certification preferred with experience working on water source heat pumps
      Cooling tower management experience
      Air handling and Energy Recovery units
      Building Automation Systems
      Experience Required: 2 to 5 yearsJob Status: Full Time
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Wedding Sales Stylist [Part-Time]
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=701&amp;ao=53356&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167738&amp;jobListingId=1405094118
    </website>
    <location>
      Erie, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      David's Bridal
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Content &amp; Design Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=702&amp;ao=65876&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167743&amp;jobListingId=1405919891
    </website>
    <location>
      King of Prussia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      ReminderMedia
    </cName>
    <description>
      Content &amp; Design ManagerReminderMedia, publishers of American Lifestyle magazine, a growing King of Prussia based company is currently hiring. We have been repeatedly recognized by Philadelphia 100 for being one of the region’s fastest growing, privately held companies. We help businesses solidify the key relationships that are driving their business. We are currently looking for a Design Manager. Responsible for the conceptualization, copy, design, and production of all cover designs, client designs, and creation of exclusive content for American Lifestyle magazine. Supervises, mentors, and trains junior and senior graphic designers in understanding and identifying clients' needs and implementing solutions. Trains design staff on proper uses and procedures of both the CRM and digital file management. Reviews and provides feedback on design team's ALM collateral. Manages ALM collateral projects and tasks within deadlines, whether assigned by print deadlines or Creative Director's approved deadline schedule. Takes initiative and offers solutions to align content with ReminderMedia’s business objectives. Develops creative briefs to communicate scope of project, business needs, and design solution. Communicates with stakeholders throughout the project lifecycle. Must have a strong sense of concept development, communication, research, problem–solving, and presentation skills. Design ability and proficiency in software applications such as Photoshop, InDesign, and Illustrator is required.Responsibilities:• Maintain a professional appearance and demeanor that reflects the company’s commitment to quality, continuous improvement and respect for individuals.• Supervise the design team to produce and prioritize jobs and, when necessary, reorganize to meet deadline changes and updates.• Lead the creative content team to create exclusive content developed in-house for publication in American Lifestyle’s digital and print platforms.• Plan a content calendar that aligns with the editorial calendar, the timing of promotion and delivery, and sales and marketing goals.• Follow systems and procedures outlined in the company manuals. Ensure Company policies &amp; procedures are followed.• Initiate hiring, handling all aspects of recruiting as assigned, and make recommendations to Creative Director.• Provide a positive, motivating example for employees. • Conduct formal performance reviews per company policy.• Initiate disciplinary measures, with management or HR approval, according to company policy when needed and dismiss production employees when all corrective attempts have failed. • Lead design team in brainstorming sessions, encouraging creativity and an open communicative environment.• Take the lead on creative projects as assigned by the Creative Director.• Project management including scheduling, setting deadlines, assigning responsibilities, and implementing post-production. Working with other departments (production, IT, customer service) for help and participation.• Collect organized research from design staff and present design solutions based on information obtained.• Review and approve creative and collateral from design staff for accuracy, neatness, and design.• Assign project leads and communicate time lines, project needs, and alterations with clients, internal and external.• Produce project descriptions and creative briefs for clients and design staff.• Train, and hold accountable, the design staff in all aspects of company procedures and CRM application.• Organize deadlines and work flow of several projects at once.• Consistently hit deadlines while managing several projects at once.• Communicate with various department heads and staff regarding needs and improvements and implement solutions. • Keep up to date with the latest print and design standards and trends in an effort to remain relevant and universally accessible. • Apply knowledge about company policies, procedures and pricing to best meet customer needs. • Participate in educational programs as required. • Perform other related duties as assigned. Qualifications:• Undergraduate degree in design-related field required.• Ten years of graphic design experience in a professional environment.• Three years of management experience.• Advanced knowledge of InDesign.• Intermediate knowledge of Illustrator and Photoshop.• Intermediate photo manipulation and color-correcting skills.• Advanced knowledge of design principles and advertising concepts.• Understanding of traditional and digital printing techniques and ability to accurately prepare and preflight jobs. • Advanced ability to apply common sense understanding to carry out instructions furnished in written, oral, or diagram form.We help business professionals connect with their core clients, on a consistent basis, in order to help them generate repeat and referral business. If you’d like to learn more about ReminderMedia, we encourage you to check us out online at www.remindermedia.com. See what we do, how we do it, and why it works!
      Apply on Career Site
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Android Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=703&amp;ao=65778&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167748&amp;jobListingId=1404660900
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Yinzcam
    </cName>
    <description>
      Who are we, and what are we looking for?
      YinzCam is the industry-leading mobile developer for sports-team apps in the United States, with clients in most major professional sports leagues such as the NFL, NBA, NHL, MLS, and even international clients such as the Australian National Rugby League. We are experiencing a period of significant growth in our business, and are looking to add more full-time Android developers.
      You will have the opportunity to work in a team of highly-skilled and experienced mobile developers to build and launch mobile apps that will be promoted by sports teams/stadiums as their official mobile app, and that will, therefore, be in the hands of millions of fans around the world. You will work closely with designers and back-end developers in a collaborative environment to develop compelling applications that provide real-time statistics and media content from official league and team source data feeds, while continuing to evolve and enhance application interfaces and improve user experience. You will also have the opportunity to innovate and explore new features such as gaming, augmented reality, etc.
      Perks
      You will have the opportunity to travel to stadiums/arenas around the country (and potentially overseas) to see how sports technology works behind the scenes. You will be exposed to the sports industry and all aspects of the company's business, including licensing, sales, advertising, revenue generation, etc. You will work in a company that invests significantly in the training of its personnel, with staff being routinely encouraged to attend professional-development and training conferences to hone and extend their skills. Benefits include competitive salaries and medical+dental insurance.
      Why are we hiring?
      We are currently expanding rapidly to take on even more clients, more teams/stadiums and more sports, including overseas, and we are looking to grow our mobile team by adding full-time Android developers to meet the demand for our products, and to bring even more innovations and features to our existing mobile offerings. Our company affords a close-knit entrepreneurial environment with every individual being exposed to, and having a tangible impact on, the company's business.
      Come join us, and you will be a part of developing the ultimate mobile experience for sports fans everywhere!
      At least 2 years' experience with Android programming
      Required API experience in intermediate to advanced UI, networking, multimedia
      Extensive knowledge of Android's resource system and experience developing for multiple screens, form factors, and densities
      Experience with RESTful web services using XML/JSON data formats
      Strong proficiency in Eclipse, ADT, command-line adb tools
      Experience with SVN, Git, or other version control systems
      Strong shell command-line and scripting skills
      Highly desirable:
      Experience with or exposure to a wide variety of Android APIs: e.g., location services, GCM, animations, gestures, in-app billing, etc.
      Knowledgeable in Android-specific memory optimization techniques, especially bitmap management
      Experience with Android WebView API, including JS interfaces
      Proficient with one or more scripting languages
      Have at least one app that you developed (or contributed substantially to) and released in Google Play
      Please send your resume and highlight
      Your overall technical skills and background
      Your relevant professional and academic experience
      Your mobile-app development skills (mention example projects, which APIs were primarily used, number of months of experience, etc.)
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      UberX Driver Partner (Part Time Independent Contractor)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=704&amp;ao=65247&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167751&amp;jobListingId=1407693449
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Uber
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Performance Engineer / PAC Engineer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=705&amp;ao=57516&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167755&amp;jobListingId=1406439744
    </website>
    <location>
      Bethlehem, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Synchronoss
    </cName>
    <description>
      Overview General Description and Responsibilities Job Responsibilities: • Performance and capacity analysis, tuning of large scale JAVA and C++ based internet applications. • Performance and capacity analysis and planning of large-scale Oracle RAC and high performance large-scale storage systems (such as Netapp). • Troubleshoot and resolve Tomcat, JAVA and C++ application server issues. • Work effectively with cross-functional teams to define technical requirements for performance enhancement and capacity planning. • Develop scripting in Shell (csh, bash), Perl or PHP, JAVA load test tools. • Define, develop and implement preemptive monitoring, support and maintenance processes and tools. • Produce data and statistical reports upon request in relation to system performance and capacity. • Participate in periodic on-call duty as well as out-of-band requests. • Occasional travel may be required.
      Technical Skills: • Minimum of 5 years of demonstrated experience in a large-scale, high-traffic web serving or wireless applications in RHEL, CentOS, OEL 5x or Unix environment. • Deep working knowledge with RHEL, CentOS, RHEL 5x and /or any flavor of Unix. • Deep working knowledge in performance analysis, tuning; capacity analysis and planning of C++, JAVA, Tomcat applications. • Deep working knowledge in performance, capacity analysis and tuning for Oracle RAC and Oracle remote replication technologies. • Deep working knowledge in performance tuning and capacity planning for large -scale storage systems. • Deep knowledge of Operating System concepts. • Good working knowledge with VMWare. • Good working knowledge in server and storage design, operational support. • Working knowledge of load balancers. • Some code development experience in C++ and JAVA applications. • Experience working with large-scale distributed systems is a definite plus.
      Other Skills: • Excellent documentation writing skills. • Excellent communication skills and interpersonal team work skills. • Affectively communicate over Phone/Skype/IM. • Ability to work independently with little supervision, looking for self-starters.
      Technical Qualification: BS in Computer-Science/Information Technology or equivalent experience
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Pharmacy Technician, Tech I Member Services
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=706&amp;ao=47682&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167762&amp;jobListingId=1405035701
    </website>
    <location>
      Wilkes-Barre, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      CVS Health
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Operations Admin I - III (Senior)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=707&amp;ao=56665&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167767&amp;jobListingId=1407397388
    </website>
    <location>
      Leetsdale, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      FedEx Ground
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      RN
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=708&amp;ao=56889&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167771&amp;jobListingId=1406220629
    </website>
    <location>
      Willow Grove, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Fresenius Medical Care - North America
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Registered Nurse \ RN Pediatric
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=709&amp;ao=62246&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167776&amp;jobListingId=1407272940
    </website>
    <location>
      Havertown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      BAYADA Home Health Care
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Personal Banker Univ
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=710&amp;ao=60211&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55fac2b9272999a7c44&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167781&amp;jobListingId=1407474318
    </website>
    <location>
      Havertown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Citizens Bank
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Sales Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=701&amp;ao=63881&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55f9eafe2cc88ad4b67&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167786&amp;jobListingId=1380420658
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      PPC Lubricants
    </cName>
    <description>
      For more than 40 years, PPC Corp. has been distributing lubricants and oils that keep cars, commercial fleets, heavy machinery and entire industries running smoothly. PPC Lubricants is excited to announce an immediate opportunity for a seasoned Sales Manager, who has a history of making connections with people, motivating others and inspiring them to achieve results. This key position will be based in the Pittsburgh area and will have responsibility for driving results through seasoned Sales Professionals based in our Western territory.
      
      This Sales Leader would be responsible for:
      
      Developing and implementing strategic sales plans to support corporate goals
      Actively managing the sales pipeline using PPC’s sales tools (excel and CRM)
      Directing sales forecasting activities and setting performance goals accordingly
      Reviewing market analysis to determine customer needs, price schedule and discount rates
      Directing staffing, training, and performance evaluations to develop and control PPC’s sales program
      Directing channel development activity and coordinates sales distribution by establishing sales territories, quotas and goals.
      Assigning sales territory to sales representatives within the established area
      Analyzing sales statistics to formulate policy and assist dealers in promoting sales
      Meeting with key clients and assisting their sales representatives with maintaining relationships and negotiating and closing deals
      Preparing sales reports showing volume, potential sales and areas of proposed client base expansion
      Monitoring activities and products of the competition
      
      In addition to a minimum of 5 years direct experience building and guiding a sales team, the successful candidate would have the ability to connect and inspire others through their stimulating verbal and written communication. They would also thrive in an environment that requires multi-tasking and a sense of urgency for achieving goals. The ability to trouble shoot problems independently and exercise leadership in changing situations is critical.
      
      If you are ready to work for a company that understands that results are achieved with and through their people, please respond with your resume and salary requirements.PPC Lubricants is an Equal Opportunity Employer
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Hair Stylist
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=702&amp;ao=64019&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fcb55f9eafe2cc88ad4b67&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697167788&amp;jobListingId=1382020853
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Sport Clips
    </cName>
    <description>
      ***STYLIST***We currently have a Stylist Position available at our Mt. Nebo Pointe (Ohio Twp.) store located in the North Hills!(270 Mt. Nebo Pointe Drive, Pittsburgh, PA 15237)We are a VERY busy, fast-paced store! Guys (our clients) love our Team! We are a friendly, outgoing, professional Team to work with! We offer a great base pay of $9/hour plus commissions and great tips! We are seeking a professional, licensed Stylist to join our Team!We offer:      Medical Benefits!
      Work in a fun, relaxed environment and wear comfortable athletic clothes!
      Chemical-Free Environment (no perms or colors)!
      Continuing Education Classes!
      Paid Vacations and Holidays!
      Great Pay ($9/hour ) plus Commissions!
      Make a change now and make Sport Clips your Career! Join our Team Today!
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Medical Biller
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=801&amp;ao=65341&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce157aacaa5120010a01e&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179352&amp;jobListingId=1399115713
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Community Psychiatric Centers
    </cName>
    <description>
      Submit mental health/psychiatric claims to insurance companies. A/R follow up with insurance carriers. Filing of charts &amp; progress notes.Office telephone reception duties and scheduling.Knowledge of medical billing and office procedures and past experiencesd working in a medical officde setting reqiuired.Full or Part time hours available in Pittsburgh (East Liberty) location.
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Licensed Massage Therapist
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=802&amp;ao=64141&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce157aacaa5120010a01e&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179354&amp;jobListingId=1383222710
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      The Body Bar
    </cName>
    <description>
      The Body Bar invites you to join our skilled team of Massage Therapists in delivering the highest quality massage &amp; spa services to both our Massage Therapy members and non-member customer base at both or either of our locations. If you are looking for a full time job or just some additional income The Body Bar is the perfect place for you!
      The Body Bar offers very flexible positions as Independent Contractors. Flexibility in your schedule allows you to pick your own hours and shifts. You can keep your current job and still enjoy extra income or work exclusively for The Body Bar. Make your own hours, working as much or as little as you like! See 2 clients a week or 10 a day! We provide the tools of the trade and clientele, in an upscale, reputable atmosphere. Plus, The Body Bar is currently offering a $250 Signing Bonus! New graduates are welcomed.
      You provide your expertise, proof of insurance &amp; licensure, availability &amp; love of massage therapy! We provide and maintain everything you need, with no additional costs to you. The Body Bar also schedules your appointment times no less than 15 minutes apart, allowing you time to regroup between sessions. Perks include free services training, fitness &amp; tanning privileges as well as discounted spa services &amp; products. The Body Bar is closed Sundays and major holidays. The Body Bar has 2 locations: McKnight Rd, North Hills &amp; Cranberry Mall, Cranberry Twp. Work at one location or both! We hope you will come tour our facilities and experience The Body Bar!
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Logistics Coordinator
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=801&amp;ao=64336&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179358&amp;jobListingId=1406822540
    </website>
    <location>
      Valley Forge, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      CompuCom
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Respiratory Therapist - PRN - Days/Evenings/Nights
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=802&amp;ao=61172&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179362&amp;jobListingId=1406809779
    </website>
    <location>
      West Reading, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Reading Health System
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      SEC Reporting Technical Accountant hot
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=803&amp;ao=64836&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179365&amp;jobListingId=1408001016
    </website>
    <location>
      Newtown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      EPAM
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Senior Product Manager
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=804&amp;ao=40339&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179368&amp;jobListingId=1405322800
    </website>
    <location>
      Warren, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Blair Corporation
    </cName>
    <description>
      Company Description With a focus on value and style, Blair® offers women's &amp; men's apparel and accessories, as well as décor and furnishings for every room in the home. Blair's Womenswear Collection features on-trend looks in a full range of sizes, designed to fit her lifestyle and her budget. Classic décor, textiles and furnishings all affordably priced make it easy to refresh and renew every room in your home. Blair is a men's resource for updated comfortable classics in extended sizes at affordable prices.
      For more information on Blair and our affiliated brands, please visit http://orchardbrands.com/
      Job Description Participates in development of Product Line strategic plans to meet marketing, merchandising, financial, and corporate growth objectives with primary responsibility for managing brand equity of one or more assigned product categories, including product conceptualization, development, fabrication, sourcing, costing, pricing strategies, selection, and merchandising in a variety of selling vehicles. Candidates for this position must have a proven track record of creatively developing, sourcing and merchandising profitable products in the assigned product categories/lines.
      ESSENTIAL DUTIES AND RESPONSIBILITIES include the following. Other duties may be assigned.
      Participates in overall merchandising strategy, market research reviews and all product/category analysis of all direct mail, telephone upsells and e-commerce selling vehicles. Works with the Merchandising Director in developing seasonal assortment plans that are in step with the vision and goals of the brand.
      Responsible for product development and merchandising for assigned product categories. Insures that merchandise selected is appropriate to strategy and targets and meets all financial goals.
      Maintains a strong presence in the marketplace by attending trade shows, reviewing fabric lines, shopping stores and catalogs, and working with vendors on product development/execution.
      Gathers, analyzes and highlights fashion and pricing trends of direct/retail competitors. Presents ideas for new business avenues and line extensions, product concepts, pricing and promotional strategies in advance of seasonal merchandising. Ensures that assigned product categories are priced competitively and offers are relevant in the marketplace and meet company g.m. goals.
      Negotiates initial costs for assigned product categories and determines selling prices.
      Collaborates closely with the Creative Team to ensure that the product vision is carried through. Responsible for leading the Creative turnover. Reviews photography and cover shots and participates in selection.
      Co-facilities in merchandising of all catalog spreads before turnovers, with emphasis on those spreads which represent assigned product categories.
      Assumes Merchandising Director responsibilities in their temporary absence.
      Develops and maintains communications and contacts to collect and analyze technical, financial, marketing, sales and product development schedule for product categories.
      Develops and delivers presentations including strategic initiatives, Topline, MORs and special projects.
      Provides merchandising guidance to E-commerce team and/or store managers members to maximize growth for additional channels.
      Declares Deletes (discontinued products available for liquidation) at seasonal reviews with inventory management team.
      Provides merchandise direction and input in developing, selecting and analyzing space advertising media. Works in conjunction with Creative to develop ads.
      Works with Customer Service to plan and facilitate seasonal product showings.
      SUPERVISORY RESPONSIBILITIES
      Directs, coaches and mentors Product Manager and/or Product Line Specialist, Merchandise Data Coordinator , Product Administrative Assistant and collaborates with all other associates located within the Merchandise Team. Evaluates Product Manager and/or Product Line Specialist, Merchandise Data Recorder and Product Administrative Assistant Carries out supervisory responsibilities in accordance with the organizations policies and applicable laws. Responsibilities include interviewing, hiring, and training employees; planning, assigning, and directing work; appraising performance; rewarding and disciplining employees; addressing complaints and resolving problems.
      Qualifications To perform this job successfully, an individual must be able to perform each essential duty satisfactorily. The requirements listed below are representative of the knowledge, skill, and/or ability required. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.
      EDUCATION and/or EXPERIENCE
      Bachelor's degree (B. A. or B. S.) from four-year college or university; and ten years merchandising experience in the direct marketing field; or equivalent combination of education and experience. Candidates must have a proven track record in creative product development and direct mail merchandising for the particular product line.
      ANGUAGE SKILLS
      Ability to read, analyze, and interpret general business periodicals and financial statements. Ability to write reports, business correspondence, and procedure manuals. Ability to effectively present information and respond to questions from groups of managers, customers, and the general public.
      MATHEMATICAL SKILLS
      Ability to calculate figures and amounts such as average costs, surcharge percentages, size scale percentages and response rates. Ability to apply concepts of basic arithmetic.
      COMPUTER SKILLS
      Proficient at operating a keyboard and mainframe software applications. Beginner to Intermediate skills with Microsoft Windows Word, Excel and Access. Experience with Forecast 21, CW Direct and Web PDMsoftware a plus.
      REASONING ABILITY
      Ability to solve practical problems and deal with a variety of concrete variables in situations where only limited standardization exists. Ability to interpret a variety of instructions furnished in written, oral, diagram, or schedule form.
      PHYSICAL DEMANDS The physical demands described here are representative of those that must be met by an employee to successfully perform the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.
      While performing the duties of this job, the employee is regularly required to sit and talk and hear. The employee frequently is required to use hands to operate a computer keyboard. The employee must occasionally lift and/or move up to 25 pounds. Specific vision abilities required by this job include close vision, distance vision, and color vision.
      WORK ENVIRONMENT The work environment characteristics described here are representative of those an employee encounters while performing the essential functions of this job. Reasonable accommodations may be made to enable individuals with disabilities to perform the essential functions.
      The noise level in the office work environment is usually moderate.
      Additional Information
      All your information will be kept confidential according to EEO guidelines.
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Primary Cell Operator (6)
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=805&amp;ao=38682&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179371&amp;jobListingId=1407754548
    </website>
    <location>
      Concordville, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Southco
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Application Engineer III
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=806&amp;ao=34032&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179375&amp;jobListingId=1406081719
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Big Heart Pet Brands
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Metalworking Account Executive
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=807&amp;ao=62771&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179379&amp;jobListingId=1405667388
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Cameron Craig Group
    </cName>
    <description>
      One of the largest direct marketers and premier distributors of Metalworking and Maintenance, Repair and Operations ("MRO") supplies to industrial customers throughout the United States. This major Company employs one of the industry's largest sales forces (over 900) and distributes industrial products from over 2000 suppliers to over 300,000 customers. The highest quality and customer service (In stock availability) exemplifies over 100 branch sales and distribution centers through-out the USA.DUTIES and RESPONSIBILITIES OF THIS POSITION:
      Supports achievement of metalworking (MW) sales and gross margin goals for their geographical area of responsibility.
      Drives accelerated MW sales growth within identified MW Impact Accounts.
      Supports Competitive Advantage Program (CAP) customer opportunities to deliver MW growth, achievement of cost savings goals and assist in the achievement of branch CAP signings.
      Maintains a MW Opportunity Funnel to track progress and success on MW Growth activities.
      Provides technical support for metalworking application opportunities to Outside Sales Associate's and MW Field Sales Rep's.
      Coordinates local supplier support for tool testing in support of OSA's and MW OSA's (FSRs).
      Assists Market Manager's and BSM's as needed in coordinating supplier involvement in market or branch meetings.
      Supports strategic supplier initiatives driven by the Product Team.
      Provides local private label technical and brand support.
      Supports the Company Culture within all the undertakings of internal and external customer engagement to ensure unity of purpose and fulfillment of Company's mission.
      Participates in special projects and performs additional duties as required.
      Required SkillsEDUCATION and EXPERIENCE:
      High school diploma required.
      Minimum 2 years of hands on machining applications experience or demonstrated proficiency in MW applications required.
      Previous field sales experience with a distributor or metalworking tooling manufacturer is preferred.
      Previous experience with machining productivity improvement or cost savings initiatives preferred.
      Well rounded proficiency across broad range of metalworking applications is preferred.
      Good communication skills are required.
      Ability to work with cross-functional teams.
      Computer proficiency in Microsoft Windows, Outlook, and Microsoft Office Programs.
      A valid driver's license and the ability to travel are required.
      EOE
      Job Location: Pittsburgh, PA   Apply on Partner Site
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      I&amp;C Maintenance Planner
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=808&amp;ao=53889&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179382&amp;jobListingId=1405574975
    </website>
    <location>
      Middletown, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Exelon
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Account Manager Financial Services
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=809&amp;ao=32078&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179385&amp;jobListingId=1407248151
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Thermo Fisher Scientific
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Director of Nursing - DON - RN
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=810&amp;ao=65524&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce15788cd85f0ac2f5c13&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179388&amp;jobListingId=1405260568
    </website>
    <location>
      Huntingdon Valley, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      HCR ManorCare
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Management Trainee
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=801&amp;ao=65726&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce157ab99bf7aeb111a7c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179391&amp;jobListingId=1404077970
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Webuyanycar.com USA
    </cName>
    <description>
      Regardless of college major or professional experience, many of our full-time employees start out in our Management Training Program. This allows everyone to learn our business from the ground up and understand how they play a significant role in seeing it succeed.
      Once you've completed your initial orientation and training, you'll be assigned to a group of branches in your home area and the hands-on training begins. You'll learn valuable business skills from capable mentors who were once in your shoes.
      Right from the start, you will actively participate in everything from sales and marketing and customer service to operations and finance. As you progress, you will be tested and evaluated to determine your proficiency in these areas. Successful completion of these tests and evaluations will result in rewards, pay increases and the opportunity for continued promotions.
      As a Management Trainee, you are empowered to make business decisions that greatly affect your career as well as the bottom line. You'll gain responsibility for developing new business and maintaining current relationships. You'll be responsible for understanding cost control, reading your branch's P&amp;L statement and understanding what it takes to run a profitable business. You will also learn how to deliver superior customer service. We will teach you how to effectively communicate, influence and interact with all types of customers, vendors and co-workers. You'll learn proper sales techniques to problem solving and conflict management. Those skills will provide you with the opportunity to market to local business partners and build solid, long-lasting relationships with key business decision-makers. In your development to become a successful manager at webuyanycar.com, you'll learn how to mentor, train, develop, manage and promote a staff of your own.
      Mandatory Requirements:
      Bachelor's degree (in a business-related field preferred.)
      Customer Service, Management, and Sales experience required.
      Must have a valid driver's license and an excellent driving record.
      Must have reliable transportation.
      Ability to project professional appearance.
      Excellent communications skills with the ability to engage in verbal interactions with customers.
      Strong sales skills
      Strong problem-solving and decision making skills.
      Properly manage employees including; training, developing, setting expectations, and disciplining.
      Must have basic computer skills and knowledge of Microsoft Office programs
      Must be able to carry out additional duties and responsibilities as assigned by management due to operational needs.
      Must have the ability to work flexible schedules, including holidays, weekends, and overtime as required
      Must be authorized to work in the United States and not require work authorization sponsorship by our company for this position now or in the future.
      Compensation:
      Base Salary
      Benefits Package (Health, Vision, Dental, 401K) offered after 90 days of continuous full-time service
      Paid Time Off and Floating Holidays
      Advancement Opportunities
      webuyanycar.com is a Drug-Free Workplace.
      All employment is contingent on successful completion of a background, reference and motor vehicle screening.
      Equal Opportunity Employer
      Apply on Career Site
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Restaurant General Manager/Asst.Manager/Shift Leaders
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=802&amp;ao=63241&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fce157ab99bf7aeb111a7c&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697179394&amp;jobListingId=1370392024
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Long John Silver's
    </cName>
    <description>
      Long John Silvers is currently looking to add General Managers/Asst Manager/Shift Leaders in the Pittsburgh market. Also Franklin, PA area. General Managers are responsible for daily operations of the store and building a strong team that believes in great food and service. Key responsabilites include::Hiring and Devoloping management and team members:Scheduling:Purchasing acording to company guide lines.:Labor control:P&amp;L review:implementing new food products per company standards.Requirements:Prior management experience for salary positionsAbility to pass background check.Must have reliable transportation
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Registered Nurse
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=901&amp;ao=65751&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7b66bc51d826d305a&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191755&amp;jobListingId=1404607046
    </website>
    <location>
      Greensburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Community Homehealth Care
    </cName>
    <description>
      Greensburg PA based agency seeking a Part-time RN (with potential for Full-time) for Medical home care visits. Daylight hours, limited weekends, competitive compensation, mileage reimbursement.
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Processing Representative
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=902&amp;ao=63162&amp;s=149&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7b66bc51d826d305a&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191757&amp;jobListingId=1403674782
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Heartland Payment Systems
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Senior Sales Representative - HR Solutions
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=901&amp;ao=32973&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191759&amp;jobListingId=1405420741
    </website>
    <location>
      Harrisburg, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Paychex
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Senior Principal Software Ninja Dell SecureWorks
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=902&amp;ao=64059&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191761&amp;jobListingId=1407762443
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Dell
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      iOS Developer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=903&amp;ao=44583&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191763&amp;jobListingId=1405651263
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Branding Brand
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Wheel Repair Detailer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=904&amp;ao=30654&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191766&amp;jobListingId=1405674017
    </website>
    <location>
      Hatfield, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      CarSense
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Store Seasonal Employee - Inside Lawn &amp; Garden
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=905&amp;ao=60428&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191768&amp;jobListingId=1406921464
    </website>
    <location>
      Butler, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Lowe's
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Franchise Sales Director, Coldwell Banker - MI, OH, PA, DE, MD, DC
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=906&amp;ao=54665&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191771&amp;jobListingId=1407848428
    </website>
    <location>
      Philadelphia, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Realogy
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Retail Sales Representative
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=907&amp;ao=57617&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191776&amp;jobListingId=1405575046
    </website>
    <location>
      Cranberry Twp, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Verizon Wireless
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Retail Sales - Women's Designer and Salon Shoes - Ross Park
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=908&amp;ao=61320&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191779&amp;jobListingId=1406335195
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Nordstrom
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      UberX Driving Partner
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=909&amp;ao=65247&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191782&amp;jobListingId=1407693479
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Uber
    </cName>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      AWS Site Reliability Engineer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=910&amp;ao=57516&amp;s=58&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7aecc152570576e69&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SR&amp;extid=1&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191784&amp;jobListingId=1406439716
    </website>
    <location>
      Bethlehem, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Synchronoss
    </cName>
    <description>
      Overview The Synchronoss Site Reliability Engineer III is primarily responsible for maintaining a highly technical and professional relationship with corporate clients during all phases of the client life-cycle. From build-out, deployment, to ongoing client support. They will also create, and maintain, all documentation needed to assure a high level of support.
      Critical Skills: • At least 5 years of Linux system administration and support experience in an enterprise IT, service provider, or telco environment. • Hands on experience including, but not limited to: o Strong AWS experience across the full breadth of AWS technologies. o Linux OS Administration, preferably RedHat Enterprise Linux (RHEL 5 and 6). o Ability to troubleshoot java server applications (Tomcat) and APIs in distributed environments. o Apache deployment, tuning, and support. o Experience with Zabbix or Nagios or similar monitoring solutions. o Ability to script in at least one of the following: Shell, Perl, or Python. o Oracle and MySQL Database administration from an operations standpoint. o Working with storage solutions (Netapp, Isilon, EMC) using iSCSI and NFS. • Proven ability to deliver a superior operations experience working directly with corporate clients technology teams and associated change management. • Enjoys learning and adapting to advancing technologies and procedural changes. • Proven incident and problem solving (troubleshooting) skills with an emphasis on a timely resolution. • Ability to coordinate and communicate effectively and professionally with other engineers, teams, and business partners. • Ability and desire to work in a team environment. • Excellent verbal, written and analytical skills, with the ability to tailor communication to the intended audience. • Experience working with ticketing systems. • Experience creating and maintaining technical documentation.
      Desired Skills: • MongoDB experience is not a firm requirement but is highly desired for this role. • Previous experience in a technical operations role. • Experience with Hadoop, Cassandra, or zookeeper. • Physical hardware and firmware exposure. • Experience with virtual server environments (KVM, Xen, VMWare, OpenVZ, etc.) • Loadbalancer support (Cisco ACE, F5 LTM, Citrix, etc.) • Experience diagnosing complex issues through packet capture analysis (Wireshark, tcpdump) • Familiarity with IP enabled storage solutions. • Familiarity with fiber channel switches and SANs (Brocade, IBM, Hitachi, HP)
      Education or Equivalent Experience: • Bachelors degree or equivalent education in related fields • Certificates of training in associated fields/equipments
      Position Type: • Full-Time/Regular
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Loan Officer / Mortgage Analyst
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=901&amp;ao=43694&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7ac6ca68fb53fefda&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191786&amp;jobListingId=1155081053
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Reliance First Capital
    </cName>
    <description>
      ​​If you have a background in SALES or TELESALES, and an entrepreneurial spirit, this position is for you!
      This is a fast paced, inside sales opportunity that offers industry leading training and an extremely lucrative compensation plan. Whether you are experienced or entry level, this is the perfect time to start a rewarding career in the mortgage industry.   Here’s what’s in it for you
      Become a part of a solid mortgage banking organization
      Competitive annual salary plus uncapped performance commissions and incentives
      Paid training (we will teach you how to become a top producing LOAN OFFICER)
      Solid support to help you “CLOSE THE DEAL" quickly
      Company Paid qualified leads daily
      Company sponsored benefit plans and paid time off benefits
      Our Loan Officers...
      Have a High School Diploma or equivalent
      Convert warm leads into sales
      Have an outgoing personality with a passion for helping people
      Possess a positive attitude, with unshakable optimism
      Enjoy building trust, developing relationships and gaining customers for life
      Excel in a telephone sales environment
      You can RELY on RELIANCE  Your SUCCESS is our SUCCESS as supported by our continued growth in today’s economy! When you join our team, you’ll have a rewarding career assisting families with their most important financial investment…have FUN…feel GREAT…and get paid WELL!
      Ready to be a part of our elite sales team?
      Reliance First Capital is an Equal Opportunity Employer. We support a drug-free work environment.​​​​​​​​​​​
    </description>
  </job>
  <job>
    <title>
      Highway Engineer
    </title>
    <website>
      http://www.glassdoor.com/partner/jobListing.htm?pos=902&amp;ao=48269&amp;s=150&amp;guid=0000014ca4fd11a7ac6ca68fb53fefda&amp;src=GD_JOB_AD&amp;t=SRFJ&amp;extid=4&amp;exst=L&amp;ist=&amp;ast=L&amp;vt=w&amp;slr=false&amp;cb=1428697191788&amp;jobListingId=1382198103
    </website>
    <location>
      Pittsburgh, PA
    </location>
    <cName>
      Gannett Fleming
    </cName>
  </job>
</jobs>
